No... impossible.
You're clearly just a frail addict to Five Stone Powder.
How could you...
How could you escape his surveillance?
And even dare to defy your master, right?
Impossible.
Too bad you'll never have the chance...
To report back anymore.
I'm acting under the orders of the Third Prince.
The prince is going against his own brother?
You better think through the consequences.
Zhu Huaichen.
I'll take your life sooner or later.
What? You want to kill him?
Hand over the whereabouts of the Dragon Jade.
And I'll spare your life.
I only blame myself for being soft-hearted at the time.
And even marrying An'er to you.
Tch.
Elder brother, wait!
Calm down.
Let me, your humble younger brother, help you question this General Li thoroughly.
The whereabouts of the Dragon Jade.
General, dying won’t be that easy for you.
If you don’t talk,
I’ll use every single torture device in this prison on you.
One by one,
I’ve spent my life on the battlefield,
How could I yield to your threats?
Take your time.
Whoever finds out the whereabouts of the Dragon Jade,
will be generously rewarded by me.
Someone! Return to the manor!
Zhi An,
sorry to keep you waiting.
Zhu Huaichen, Duan Yurou,
I’m curious to see what tricks you’re up to this time.
Zhi An,
you look stunning today.
What’s wrong?
It’s nothing.
Zhi An,
let’s drink the wedding wine, shall we?
So, this is my wedding night?
So disgusting.
Zhi'an, you shouldn't have to face all this.
Assassin!
Huaichen, what happened?
Huaichen, is there a third person in this room besides us?
You're overthinking it.
Apart from you and me,
there's no one else here.
Guards!
There's an assassin!
Third Prince!
What happened?
Third Prince, what happened?
His eyes have been injured! Quickly, summon the imperial physician!
Hurry!
Quick, treat the prince!
Leave, and capture the assassin!
Yes, capture the assassin!
Why is Huaichen so enraged?
Are you resenting me?
How could I?
Today is, after all, our big day.
Wait here for me to return.
Could it be that her eyesight has been restored?
Zhu Huaichen!
Enjoy this moment.
Your suffering has just begun.